[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What hyena species is the largest surviving on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Spotted Hyena", "incorrect_answers": ["Aardwolf", "Striped Hyena", "Brown Hyena"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the host as well as the winner of the first Soccer World Cup which was was held in 1930?", "correct_answer": "Uruguay", "incorrect_answers": ["Brazil", "Italy", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Claires sex crazed sister who is in love with Jeremy in the hilarious movie Wedding Crashers?", "correct_answer": "Gloria", "incorrect_answers": ["Toni", "Laura", "Janis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following line belongs to which character from The Crow: Our friend T-bird wont be joining us this evening on account of a slight case of death.?", "correct_answer": "Top Dollar", "incorrect_answers": ["Funboy", "Tin Tin", "Eric Draven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ghost of the Roman Emperor Caligula was said to haunt this place.", "correct_answer": "The Lamian Gardens of Rome", "incorrect_answers": ["Basilica di San Giovanni in Laterano", "Amphitheatrum Castrense", "Great Synagogue of Rome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which of these factors does the total amount of water on Earth at a certain moment depend?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Time of the day", "Distance from the Sun", "Season"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The world record for the oldest goldfish is 49 years.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In aromatherapy, essential oils are often used to enhance the mood.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Cal get a new nickname before he marries Carley in Talladega Nights?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does demophobia mean?", "correct_answer": "Fear of crowds", "incorrect_answers": ["Fear of insanity", "Fear of demons", "Fear of trees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what actor are Greg and his supposed son Jorge compared in the 2004 movie Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "Marlon Brando", "incorrect_answers": ["Omar Sharif", "All of these", "Al Pacino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chicks on a raft with blowout patches refers to what?", "correct_answer": "Eggs on toast with pancakes", "incorrect_answers": ["Western omelet with french toast", "Scrambled eggs and sausage", "Fried chicken and mashed potatoes"]}]